PABLO JAVIER MONTICOLI

PROGRAMMER



+54 9 3525507920

 $>\!\!<$

pablomonticoli@hotmail.com GitHub PJMonticoli

PROFILE SUMMARY

Programming Technician with over 1 year of experience in the full software development cycle. I stand out for my ability to quickly adapt to new technologies, enabling me to collaborate effectively in teams and ensure the delivery of high-quality software.

EDUCATION

National Technological University

2021-2023

Graduated as a Programming Technician.

National University of Cordoba

2018-2021

Accounting. Incomplete (18 subjects passed).

Nuestra Señora del Rosario del Milagro

2012-2017

Bachelor of Economics and Administration.

SOFTWARE TOOLS

Angular SQL/NoSQL

Spring Framework

HTML

.NET Framework

Scrum Methodology

CSS

C#

Supabase

JavaScript/TypeScript

Java

Git

Python

NodeJs(ExpressJs)

Docker

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

September 2023 – Present

José Guma S.A, Colonia Caroya

• Currently undertaking an internship in the Systems Area. Working with .NET, C#, SQL/NoSQL, Angular and Python. I'm involved in application development and database management, collaborating on process optimization and technical issue resolution.

Freelance E-commerce

Freelancer

February 2023 - August 2023

 Designed and developed an online store for a chocolate shop, optimizing user experience and enhancing purchase functionality.

Administrative and Accounting

José Guma S.A, Colonia Caroya

June 2017 – August 2017

• Internships involved in administrative and accounting roles, assisting in the management of administrative and accounting tasks, supporting in report preparation and documentation.

LANGUAGES

- Spanish: Native
- English: Advanced

Cambridge English: Preliminary English Test. Currently attending advanced English classes at English in Company Academy.



Universidad Tecnológica Nacional Facultad Regional Córdoba

El que suscribe: DECANO de la FACULTAD REGIONAL CÓRDOBA ING. HÉCTOR RUBÉN MACAÑO, certifica que MONTÍCOLI, PABLO JAVIER, DNI Nro. 42162165, Legajo: 113491, con título anterior Bachiller en Economía y Administración, expedido por Instituto Nuestra Señora del Rosario del Milagro de Jesús María - Provincia de Córdoba, ha obtenido las siguientes calificaciones correspondientes a la carrera de TECNICATURA UNIVERSITARIA EN PROGRAMACIÓN, Plan 2003.-

ASIGNATURAS	Cursó			Fecha	Libro	Folio	Facultad	Observationes
	el Año	N°	Letras	Aprob.	Libro	rono	racuitad	Observaciones
Arquitectura y Sistemas Operativos	2021	7	siete	10/12/21	T.74	139	FRC	P 2003 2Cuat
Estadística	2021	9	nueve	09/12/21	T.74	98	FRC	P 2003 2Cuat
Inglés I	2021	10	diez	05/07/21	T.73	5	FRC	P 2003 1Cuat
Inglés II	2021	10	diez	29/11/21	T.73	550	FRC	P 2003 2Cuat
Laboratorio de Computación I	2021	7	siete	28/07/21	T.73	237	FRC	P 2003 1Cuat
Laboratorio de Computación II	2021	8	ocho	24/11/21	T.73	447	FRC	P 2003 2Cuat
Matemática	2021	8	ocho	25/11/21	T.73	481	FRC	P 2003 1Cuat
Metodología de la Investigación	2021	9	nueve	24/11/21	T.73	451	FRC	P 2003 2Cuat
Programación I	2021	6	seis	27/07/21	T.73	208	FRC	P 2003 1Cuat
Programación II	2021	8	ocho	23/11/21	T.73	403	FRC	P 2003 2Cuat
Sistemas de Procesamiento de Datos	2021	9	nueve	30/07/21	T.73	303	FRC	P 2003 1Cuat
Diseño y Administración de Bases de Datos	2022	9	nueve	06/12/22	T.77	206	FRC	P 2003 2Cuat
Elementos de Investigación Operativa	2022	10	diez	04/07/22	T.76	18	FRC	P 2003 1Cuat
Laboratorio de Computación III	2022	10	diez	05/07/22	T.76	56	FRC	P 2003 1Cuat
Laboratorio de Computación IV	2022	9	nueve	06/12/22	T.77	208	FRC	P 2003 2Cuat
Legislación	2022	7	siete	07/12/22	T.77	240	FRC	P 2003 2Cuat
Metodología de Sistemas I	2022	9	nueve	25/11/22	T.77	102	FRC	P 2003 2Cuat
Organización Contable de la Empresa	2022	10	diez	07/07/22	T.76	94	FRC	P 2003 1Cuat
Organización Empresarial	2022	8	ocho	27/07/22	T.76	233	FRC	P 2003 1Cuat
Práctica Profesional		9	nueve	28/07/23	T.79	161	FRC	P 2003 Sin Cursar
Programación III	2022	8	ocho	04/07/22	T.76	14	FRC	P 2003 1Cuat
							Trush 1	Lancage 2 - 1

HOJA I/I

ASIGNATURAS	Cureh	Calificación Nº Letras		Fecha	12.00		Franks.	
	el Año	N°	Letras	Aprob.	Libro	Folio	Facultad	Observaciones
								4 7 10
						18	1/16	end of base 1984
		140-140						The can be to the
THE PERSON NAMED OF THE PARTY.	-	17.77	F-7-10	ALTERNATION OF THE PARTY OF THE	7777			7-17-20-20-7
adosti sutabu ulifii, nga 1946 i	Heren.	A A S	Lalia		لفطال المستع		distant.	ت يونونولارك أعادت
Marial Shensell (Income)			136		insin a		11	Louisian Liberton Berlie
					217		LA ALL D	12.12.18.6.11-1.1
a eleganical lightness of				74 H	i her			2.8.3.12.(2012)
THE STATE OF THE SECOND SECOND		Lank w						the matterial of the state
The second second								and the same of th
The state of the s								
ing ready of a series								
		1-						
						-		

Las calificaciones obtenidas por el estudiante en asignaturas que fueron registradas hasta el 31 de Marzo de 2018, conforme a la escala de calificaciones de la Ordenanza 1149 (aprobado, calificaciones 4 o superiores), son ponderadas para el cálculo del promedio por la ecuación que figura en Ordenanza Nº 1566. No se ponderan los insuficientes (calificaciones 1, 2 y 3).

Ha concluido el plan de estudios correspondiente a la carrera TECNICATURA UNIVERSITARIA EN PROGRAMACIÓN plan de 2 años, con un promedio general de 8,57 (ocho con cincuenta y siete centésimos), egresando el día 28 de julio de 2023.-

Para que conste y a pedido del interesado se le expide el presente certificado, sin enmiendas ni raspaduras, en CÓRDOBA el 19 de diciembre de 2023, para los fines que estime corresponder.

U.T.N.

Secretario Académico Ing. Roberto M. Muñoz

Liliana A. Fernandez Directora Académica

Buenos Aires, 19 de diciembre de 2023-

Decano

Ing. Héctor A. Macaño

Firma del interesado

Verificado que las firmas que anteceden son auténticas, y controlado el presente certificado, el Consejo Superior de la Universidad Tecnológica Nacional, por Resolución Nro.: 3599 de fecha 13 de diciembre de 2023 aprueba el otorgamiento del diploma que lo acredita como: TÉCNICO UNIVERSITARIO EN PROGRAMACIÓN f

Secretaria Académica
Ing. LILIANA RAQUEL CUENCA PLETSCH

Ing. HAROLO TOMÁS AVETTA

00099502





Cambridge English Entry Level Certificate in ESOL International (Entry 3) (Preliminary)*

This is to certify that

PABLO JAVIER MONTÍCOLI

has been awarded

Pass-----

in the

Preliminary English Test

Council of Europe Level B1

Overall Score	141
Reading	132
Writing	148
Listening	134
Speaking	151

Date of Examination JUNE (S1) 2017

Place of Entry CORDOBA

Reference Number 176AR6125008

Accreditation Number 500/2414/0

*This level refers to the UK National Qualifications Framework

Sanl Name

Saul Nassé Chief Executive

Date of Issue 21/07/17

Certificate Number 0058119276

Regulated by

Ofqual

For more information see http://register.ofqual.gov.uk



DP835

